Guide to the Edward W. Kelley, Jr. Federal Reserve papers, 1986-2010 MS 492
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: FOMC "Current Economic & Financial Conditions" & "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, 1987-2001, 75067
  - 1996-1998, 75071 (Box 14)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, August-December, 1996; 79278 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, January-March, 1997; 79279 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, May-June, 1997; 79280 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, August-September, 1997; 79281 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, November-December, 1997; 79282 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, 1997; 79283 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, January-March, 1998; 79284 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, May-June, 1998; 79285 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, August-September, 1998; 79286 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, November-December, 1998; 79287 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, 1998; 79288 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - 1999-2001, 75072 (Box 15)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, January-March 1999; 79289 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, May-June 1999; 79290 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, August-September 1999; 79291 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, November-December 1999; 79292 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, 1999; 79293 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, January-March 2000; 79294 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, May-June 2000; 79295 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, August-September 2000; 79296 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, November-December 2000; 79297 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives" reports, 2000; 79298 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, January-March 2001; 79299 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, May-June 2001; 79300 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, August-September 2001; 79301 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - FOMC "Current Economic and Financial Conditions" reports, October 2001; 79302 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - FOMC "Monetary Policy Alternatives", 2001; 79303 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Series IV: "Current Economic Conditions" publication, 1988-2001, 75073
  - 1988-1994, 75074 (Box 16)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", January-May 1988; 79304 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", June-November 1988; 79305 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", January-June 1989; 79306 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", August-December 1989; 79307 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", January-March 1990; 79308 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", May-June 1990; 79309 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", August-December 1990; 79310 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", January-April 1991; 79311 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", June-July 1991; 79312 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", September-November 1991; 79313 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", January-April 1992; 79314 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", June-July 1992; 79315 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", September-October 1992; 79316 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", November 1992; 79317 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", January-April 1993; 79318 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", July-August 1993; 79320 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", October-November 1993; 79321 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", January-April 1994; 79322 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", June-July 1994; 79323 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", September-November 1994; 79324 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - 1995-2001, 79319 (Box 17)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", January-March 1995; 79325 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", May-July 1995; 79326 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", September-November 1995; 79327 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", March-April 1996; 79328 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", June-July 1996; 79329 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", September-November 1996; 79330 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", January-April 1997; 79331 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", June-July 1997; 79332 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", September-December 1997; 79333 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", January-June 1998; 79334 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", September-October 1998; 79335 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", November-December 1998; 79336 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", January-April 1999; 79337 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", June-August 1999; 79338 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", September-October 1999; 79339 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", November 1999; 79340 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", January-April 2000; 79341 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", June-September 2000; 79342 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", October 2000; 79343 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", November 2000; 79344 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", February-April 2001; 79345 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", June-July 2001; 79346 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - "Summary of Commentary on Current Economic Conditions by Federal Reserve District", September-November 2001; 79347 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Series V: Federal Reserve Board Oral History, 2010, 164701
  - Interview of Edward W. Kelley, Jr. - transcript and audio cd, September 22, 2010; 164702 (Box 17, Folder 24)